Come on friends, welcome all of you once again to
your own channel friends,
today I am bringing you mustard oil, I
mean, there is tremendous growth here,
soon an office can
give profit here, friends, which
Reliance group, friends, so
you can see it here, the product of Anil Ambani's company, yes friends,
when the name of Dhani Tata is added to it, there was a huge crowd gathered
to buy it, yes friends,
today for the
fourth consecutive day, the upper circuit is being
seen here in Reliance shares, the company's share is approaching 1745 with a
rise of 4.80 percent till now,
you must be seeing it,
friends, which is
showing thyroid in it for four consecutive days, yes friends,
you can see here that it is within 5 days, you have seen
it sent on the proposal here,
friends, so you
can see a lot of growth in this company soon, so
let's talk a little about it, so
in Reliance Capital shares, but today for the
fourth consecutive day, priority has been given.  It has been seen that
yesterday the stock of the company was
seen closing at 16075,
which means that you got to see that Solar closed at 75 paise here
and as you
can see here, after a rise of 80 paise,
today its price will be
seen at 1745 and before this, it was seen
here on Wednesday, Tuesday and Monday,
so lastly the stock of the company has
seen a rise here due to the proposal of people from Chat Addiction and here, so
finally, there is a rise in this market, that is, let
us see the office, then the
rise in the stock of that company is being seen after seeing the news in
which it was said
that the names of
big companies like Dhani Tata have come up to buy Reliance Capital,
real friends,
it came to light that Reliance Capital Limited has
bid on 54 companies,
among these companies big companies like Tata, Tata
Nano, Tata AC, ICICI Lombard,
HDFC Ergo and Nippon Life
Insurance are
included here, so after this news, the
stock of the company has seen a strong rise.  We are seeing a boom,
friends, if you
show the chart panel on the fifth, you can see here, so
in 5 years, when your time comes, you can
see the message 'Send when your time comes', which used to be
5662, today we are
seeing 1745 messages here, I will
tell you that in the last 5 years, there has been a lot of
decline, whereas if we talk about the last one
year, then you can see here, so
in the last one year, there is such a good
recovery here, the address is up to 55 percent, the
company has reached this state within this year,
whereas if I talk from January till now, then
you can see here, you will
see the profit tax here, whereas if
I talk about six months, then
you can see here, there
is a slight decline on the website and here, but
within a month, we have encouraged it,
237 percent, there is a boom here,
meaning that since the last one month,
companies have been making a good recovery here,
now you can see here in the last 5 days,
so you  And here you will see a rise on the rota
and today also you
can see here that a rise of four and a half to five percent is being
seen here today, which
means that the company is
making a lot of requests on itself here,
yes friends, companies can give a lot of profit,
so if you want, you
can take another one in this, then you can book better profit in the doctor,
I am busy with these people, friends, so
friends, that was enough for you, you can think about it, so
how did you like it, you will have to tell us in the comment section
that in today's video, so many
Naxalites were found, they were updated with this
token, till then goodbye